<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Arif Ahmed</title>
    <link>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Arif Ahmed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 18:05:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://arifahmed1995.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Summer of Code 2017 with SymPy</title>
      <link>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/projects/contributions/gsoc17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/projects/contributions/gsoc17/</guid>
      <description>This project implemented a module in SymPy which provides the ability to integrate arbitrary polynomials over 2D, 3D polytopes. Using Generalized Stokes&amp;rsquo; Theorem and Euler&amp;rsquo;s Theorem the integration over a given polytope is reduced to integration over its faces and then edges. This technique avoids using a 3D quadrature which would otherwise be computationally expensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Summer of Code 2018 with CERN-HSF</title>
      <link>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/projects/contributions/gsoc18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/projects/contributions/gsoc18/</guid>
      <description>Evaluated the dependencies of the TMath Functions already available in ROOT. Added a vectorized implementation of the ROOT::TMath functions in VecCore. Benchmarked performance in different architectures and instruction sets. Integrated the new VecCore implementations in ROOT and added benchmarks.
Major Commit for ROOT
Merged PR for ROOT benchmarks
Minor Commits for VecCore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organically DevOps: Building Quality and Security into the Software Supply Chain at Liberty Mutual</title>
      <link>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/publications/alldaydevops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/publications/alldaydevops/</guid>
      <description>This talk looked at Liberty Mutual’s transformation to Continuous Integration, Continuous Delivery, and DevOps. For a large, heavily regulated industry, this task can not only be daunting, but viewed by many as impossible. Often, organizations try to reduce the friction through micro-fixes, but Eddie’s team asked how to change the culture to reduce the friction and concluded with the following final points:
 Don’t mandate DevOps. Give employees the chance to master their discipline with examples to set and follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modeling non-linear audio effects with end-to-end deep neural networks</title>
      <link>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/projects/creations/distortion_dnn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/projects/creations/distortion_dnn/</guid>
      <description>Here is a link to the paper.
The main aim of was to find a general purpose end-to-end deep neural network to perform modeling of nonlinear audio effects. I also found the usage of Soft Adaptive Activation Function(SAAF) quite interesting. Had never encountered an adaptive activation before and was curious about implementing it.
The network consists of 1D convolutional filters to expand the input into multiple channels, then max pooling to extract out the most important aspects of the channel output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spectral-Spatial Classification of Hyperspectral Images</title>
      <link>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/projects/creations/hyperspectral/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/projects/creations/hyperspectral/</guid>
      <description>Here is a link to the paper.
I primarily did this project to implement an image processing algorithm from scratch. OpenCV does not have the implementation of Edge-Preserving filter for more than three channels when I did this project.
Independent Components Analysis(ICA) is first performed across the channels to separate out the information present in the image. Gaussian Filter is applied, this process is referred to as small structure removal in the algorithm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music Generation using a Differentiable Neural Computer</title>
      <link>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/projects/creations/music_dnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/projects/creations/music_dnc/</guid>
      <description>Here is a link to the paper.
This was a formal project I did along with Sudeep Katakol in my last semester of college. We were trying to improve on PerformanceRNN. Wrestling around with the architecture, intermediate layers and/or removing and adding linkages to the memory bank, none of it seemed to work that well. We presented our findings and code so far and left the project to be continued by the upcoming batch of students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study Project: Multi-Agent Diverse GANs</title>
      <link>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/projects/creations/mad_gan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/projects/creations/mad_gan/</guid>
      <description>Multi-Agents GANs are a simple modification of the original architecture. Instead of one generator, there are multiple ones and they provide for a realistic variance in output. Each of the generators eventually collapse to different peaks of the distribution to be learned. Detailed information can be found in the report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forcing Visits to use SSL</title>
      <link>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/blog/force-ssl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/blog/force-ssl/</guid>
      <description>Intro Doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter whether it&amp;rsquo;s a CakePHP app for a client, your own personal CMS, or any other web based application. If your passing around passwords or other sensitive info you should really implement SSL. SSL provides 2 main perks to your visitors.
 First it encrypts all communication that flies across the web. This prevents curious or devious billies from getting your secrets. Secondly it ensures to the user that your server is in fact who it claims, and not a nasty &amp;lsquo;man in the middle&amp;rdquo; attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arifahmed1995.github.io/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
[outputs] home = [&amp;#34;HTML&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;JSON&amp;#34;] Searching additional fileds To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>